<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>AVbin</title>
    <link>http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Home.html</link>
    <description>AVbin is a thin cross-platform wrapper around FFmpeg’s video and audio decoding functionality, providing binary compatibility for applications and languages that need it.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AVbin was originally created for the Pyglet project as its media decoding/decompression library,  though others may find AVbin useful as well.</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Home_files/istock_000003140881medium.jpg</url>
      <title>AVbin</title>
      <link>http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Home.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>AVbin 8</title>
      <link>http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Entries/2011/12/10_AVbin_8.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e3040a0-7cfc-4fc9-ade3-eb446bb2d7b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 21:05:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Entries/2011/12/10_AVbin_8_files/index1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Media/object008_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:183px; height:137px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;I am proud to announce AVbin 8, the first full release since 2008.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To all those who pointed me in the right direction on mailing lists and forums:  Thank you!!!  I would like to specifically mention Alex Holkner, who created this project in the first place, and Micah Richert, whose shoulders I stood on for this release.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AVbin 8 Highlights&lt;br/&gt;	-	Established which platforms were going to be supported going forward (added Win64 and OS X 64-bit Intel; dropped OS X 32-bit PPC)&lt;br/&gt;	-	Created development/build environments for each platform&lt;br/&gt;	-	Successfully compiled/released a build for each platform&lt;br/&gt;	-	Migrated from svn on Google Project to git on Github&lt;br/&gt;	-	Created a new project web site&lt;br/&gt;	-	28 commits&lt;br/&gt;	-	Approximately 15 issues closed...though mostly since they just don’t apply any more.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Known Issues with AVbin 8:&lt;br/&gt;	-	The version of FFmpeg used is one year old, and has known bugs and security problems&lt;br/&gt;	-	The AVbin binaries have not been tested internally.&lt;br/&gt;	-	The AVbin binaries have not been tested with Pyglet.&lt;br/&gt;	-	It is known that the build doesn’t actually work for a lot of file formats you would expect it to on at least one platform (win32)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The previous release was based on a 3-year old FFmpeg revision.  That revision of FFmpeg had even more bugs and security problems than the newer one we used (though I bet that version of AVbin was more functional).  When I took over as the new maintainer almost exactly a month ago, I accepted the generous offer of Micah Richert to use his personal build he had put together a year ago as a starting point.  Since using the newest code was not a goal for this release, I simply used the exact revision that Micah used, to minimize the already considerable effort it was taking to get this project resurrected.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I’ve put together a &lt;a href=&quot;../Roadmap.html&quot;&gt;Roadmap&lt;/a&gt; for things to accomplish for AVbin 9.  Check it out!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;~ Nathan</description>
      <enclosure url="http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Entries/2011/12/10_AVbin_8_files/index1.jpg" length="126612" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVbin project migrated to Github</title>
      <link>http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Entries/2011/11/24_AVbin_project_migrated_to_Github.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9b268ff-ec96-41c5-b2ca-ca57cd24dfc8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 14:41:31 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Entries/2011/11/24_AVbin_project_migrated_to_Github_files/Migrating-Snow-Geese-1-K0646XOAV8-1600x1200.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Media/object004_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:183px; height:137px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Welcome to the new AVbin site!  AVbin has moved from subversion on Google code to Git on Github.  We hope that the move promotes more collaboration and participation in the project.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://avbin.github.com/AVbin/Home/Entries/2011/11/24_AVbin_project_migrated_to_Github_files/Migrating-Snow-Geese-1-K0646XOAV8-1600x1200.jpg" length="119239" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
